Contact

arunjamessahadeo@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/arunsahadeo-00836883 (LinkedIn) arunsahadeo.github.io/ (Personal)

Top Skills

SQL

Web Development

Tableau

Languages

German (Limited Working)

Arun Sahadeo

Data Engineer

London, England, United Kingdom

Summary

Data and software professional, experienced in data visualisation (Tableau / Python), database development and maintenance (MySQL / MSSQL / Oracle / BigQuery), Linux server maintenance (centOS /Ubuntu), web server configuration / administration (Apache / NGINX).

Conversant with both Windows and *nix (macOS and Linux flavours including Ubuntu).

Experience

Tata Consultancy Services
Data Engineer
July 2022 - Present (1 year 5 months)
Leamington Spa, England, United Kingdom

Wirebox

Full Stack Developer November 2015 - July 2022 (6 years 9 months)

Education

North Warwickshire and South Leicestershire College NCFE Level 2 Certificate in Understanding Data Protection and Data Security, Information Technology (2019 - 2019)

3aaa Apprenticeships

BTEC Level 3 Advanced Apprenticeship for IT, Software, Web and Telecoms Professionals \cdot (2015 - 2016)

Harrow College

BTEC Level 3 Extended Diploma in Creative Media Production · (2013 - 2015)

Bishop Ramsey CofE

A-level, German, Religious Studies, English Literature · (2011 - 2013)

Bishop Ramsey CofE

11 GCSEs including English, Maths and Science · (2006 - 2011)